crazy4jigsaws.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Crazy4Jigsaws.com

## Introduction

Crazy4Jigsaws cares about your privacy. Below is an overview of the information we collect, what we use the information for, and instructions on how to opt-out of our email newsletter. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please [contact us](http://www.crazy4jigsaws.com/contact/). 

## Information We Collect

For each visitor to this website, our web server automatically recognizes: 

  * Your IP address
  * Browser version
  * Operating system
  * Date and time of access
  * Referring site or search engine

We collect and store personal information about users who sign up for free and premium membership, including: 

  * Email address
  * Name and billing information
  * Information about website actions (such as how many jigsaws each user has solved)
  * Information volunteered by visitors (such as survey information)

## Use

General visitor data is stored in a log file on our server. This data is not used to personally identify individuals and is only used to: 

  * Analyze website traffic
  * Anonymously analyze user actions
  * Provide statistical data to our advertisers and partners

Personal identifying information, such as your email address, is only used for internal purposes and is not disclosed or sold to third-parties. We also use this information to customize website content based on browsing preferences as well as provide relevant marketing opportunities.

Other non-personally identifying information is used for statistical analysis and may be shared with third parties. 

## Email Privacy

The email addresses collected from our free and premium members are not sold or disclosed to any third party. We use the email addresses to send announcements to members who request our newsletters. Email addresses may also be used to send important account information, such as passwords, when necessary. Users may change their email newsletter settings at <http://www.crazy4jigsaws.com/account/>.

## Cookies

We use cookies to store visitor preferences, allow members to login, and ensure that visitors do not repeatedly view the same ads. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Cookies are required in order to login to this website. 

## Data Security

We respect the security of your data and have taken appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data collected during the use of this website. 

## Changes

Any future changes in our privacy policy will be posted on this page. If you are concerned about how your information is used, check this page periodically for updates.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or need assistance opting-out from our email newsletters please contact us via email at support@crazy4jigsaws.com or by postal mail at: 

Crazy4Jigsaws  
PO Box 2854  
Cypress, Texas 77429
